Guide to the Winterhouse Art and Design Collection of Volume 1 Number 1
Yale University Arts Library
- Examples, 1919-2011; Series II
  - SABR Review of Books: A Forum of Baseball Literary Opinion. Volume One: Number One. Cooperstown, New York: Society for American Baseball Research, 1986. pp. 112. (Box 5, Folder 191)
    Edited by Paul Adomites.
    Contributions by Roger Kahn, Jim Kaplan, Peter Levine and Eugene Murdock.
    Article of note: "The Negro Leagues Revisited."
  - San Rocco. #0. Dorsoduro, Venice, Italy, Summer 2010. pp. 152. (Box 5, Folder 192)
    Edited by Matteo Ghidoni.
    Contributions by Joana Rafael, Marco Brizzi and Kersten Geers.
    Article of note: "Broadcasting Architecture."
    Design by Pupilla Grafik and Salottobuono.
  - Scope: A Journal of Science. Number One. Perth, Australia: University of Western Australia, September 1946. pp. 48. (Box 5, Folder 193)
    Edited by Ronald Strahan.
    Contributions by Reginald Hare, R.H. Leary and S. Strickland.
    Article of note: "Physics and the War: Camouflage."
  - Seed: Beneath The Surface. Premier Issue. Montreal: Seed Group, 2001. pp. 176. (Box 5, Folder 194)
    Edited by Adam Bly.
    Contributions by David Aris, Iona Pelovska and Brian Finke.
    Article of note: "Me."
    Design by Alex-Yves Pepin.
  - Shirim: A Jewish Poetry Journal. Volume One. Los Angeles: Shirim Intermedia, Fall 1982. pp. 32. (Box 5, Folder 195)
    Edited by Marc Steven Dworkin.
    Contributions by Yehuda Amichai, Marcia Falk and Haim Gouri.
    Poem of note: "At Israel's Bedeken."
    Cover art by Sandy Dubrow.
  - Shuffle, Boil: A Magazine of Poets and Music. Number One. Berkeley: Listening Chamber, Winter 2002. pp. 48. (Box 5, Folder 196)
    Edited by David Meltzer and Steve Dickison.
    Contributions by Michael Gizzi, Alastair Johnston and Michael Rothenberg.
    Article of note: "The Latin Side of Monk."
    Design by Steve Dickison.
  - Signature: A Quadrimestrial of Typography and Graphic Arts. Number One. London: Signature, November 1935. pp. 64. (Box 5, Folder 197)
    Edited by Oliver Simon.
    Contributions by Harry Carter, Paul Nash and Eric Ravilious.
    Article of note: "A Sanctuary of Printing: The Record Room at the University Press, Oxford."
  - Six Degrees. Issue 1. North Carolina State University, February 2006. pp. 82.. (Box 5, Folder 198)
    Edited by Caroline Okun.
    Contributions by Jenna Bailey, Matt Balla and Heath Beckett.
    Article of note: "Assumption."
    Design by Plastiekhart.
  - Slash Magazine: A Quarterly for the Extra Observant. Issue One. Savannah, Georgia: Slash Magazine, 2004. pp. 112. (Box 5, Folder 199)
    Edited by K. Hinton.
    Contributions by Nohemi Dicuru, Dustin Amery Hostetler and Conrad Mcgregor.
    Article of note: "Killer Toys."
  - Slate. Volume One: Number One. Redmond, WA: Microsoft, September 1996. pp. 60. (Box 5, Folder 200)
    Edited by Michael Kinsley and Jodie Allen.
    Contributions by Anne Hollander, Paul Krugman and Michael Wood.
    Article of note: "The Olympic Gene Pool."
    Design by Ian Adelman.
  - The Smith. Volume 1: Issue 1. New York: The Smith, February 1964. pp. 64. (Box 5, Folder 201)
    Edited by Harry Smith.
    Contributions by Bran Jordan, Menke Katz and Charles Philbrick.
    Article of note: "The Truth Business."
    Design by Stephen Dwoskin.
  - Spy. New York: Spy Publishing Partners, October 1986. pp. 64. (Box 5, Folder 202)
    Edited by Kurt Andersen and E. Graydon Carter.
    Contributions by Roy Blount Jr., Holly Brubach and Patty Marx.
    Article of note: "Downhill from Here."
  - Strange Attractor. Journal One. Wiltshire, England: Strange Attractor, January 2004. pp. 260. (Box 5, Folder 203)
    Edited by Mark Pilkington.
    Contributions by Mike Jay, Tiomothy d'Arch Smith and Helen John.
    Article of note: "Montague Summers, the Marquis de Sade and the Curious World of the British Society for the Study of Sex Psychology."
    Design by Alison Hutchinson.
  - The Stürung. Volume One: Issue One. New York: Columbia University. pp. 32., undated (Box 7, Folder 264)
    Edited by Philip Bird.
    Contributions by Brandon Webb, Divya Mehra and Matthew Berry.
    Article of note: "Fantasy Draft."
  - Sync. Volume One: Issue One. Dallas: Image Bank, 1998. pp. 96. (Box 5, Folder 204)
    Edited by Guy Lesser.
    Contributions by Joanna Levin, Bill McKibben and John Updike.
    Article of note: "The Cathedrals of Today."
    Design by Carla Miller.
  - Talk. Issue One. New York: Talk, September 1999. pp. 254. (Box 5, Folder 205)
    Edited by Tina Brown.
    Contributions by Michael Birt, Tucker Carlson and Patrick Demarchelier.
    Article of note: "I Wanna Dance with the Strawberry Girl."
    Design by Lesley Vinson.
  - Task. Number 1. 2007. pp. 64. (Box 5, Folder 206)
    Edited by Emmet Byrne, Alex DeArmond and Jon Sueda.
    Contributions by Geoff Halber, Kristina Bell and Kate McKinney.
    Article of note: "Re-purposing the Apple Store."
    Design by Emmet Bryne, Alex DeArmond and Jon Sueda.
  - Tel Quel. Number One. Paris: Éditions du Seuil, Spring 1960. pp. 96. (Box 5, Folder 207)
    Edited by Jacques Coudol Boisrouvray, Jean-Edern Hallier, Jean-René Huguenin, Renaud Matignon and Philippe Sollers.
    Contributions by Francis Ponge, Claude Simon and Virginia Woolf.
    Article of note: "Flaubert et la sensibilité modern."
  - Temblor: Contemporary Poets. Number 1. North Hollywood, 1985. pp. 137. (Box 5, Folder 208)
    Edited by Leland Hickman.
    Contributions by Kenneth Irby, Gerald Burns and John Clarke.
    Article of note: "Bracketing in City Thickets."
    Design by Arthaus Studio.
  - Terrazzo: A Biannual Publication on Architecture and Design. Number One. Milan: Terrazzo, Fall 1988. pp. 160. (Box 7, Folder 265)
    Edited by Barbara Radice.
    Contributions by Andrea Branzi, Herbert Muschamp and Ettore Sottsass.
    Article of note: "Outside the Avant-Garde."
    Design by Christoph Radl.
  - Textfield Magazine. Volume One: Issue One. Los Angeles: Textfield Press, Winter 2003. pp. 114. (Box 5, Folder 209)
    Edited by Jonathan Maghen.
    Contributions by Yuji Adachi, Piero Golia and Textfield Research Institute.
    Article of note: "Our Websites, the Art of Our Times."
    Design by Textfield Graphik.
  - The Thousands: A Magazine of Poetry and General Opinion. Number One. Minneapolis: Thousands Press, Fall 2001. pp. 96. (Box 5, Folder 210)
    Edited by Robert Bly.
    Contributions by Bhartrihari, Hafez and Tomas Tranströmer.
    Article of note: "Six Disciplines That Intensify Poetry."
    Design by Sarah Kirkwood.
  - Thrasher Fanzine. Issue #1. pp. 80., undated (Box 6, Folder 211)
    Edited by Sam Korman and Israel Lund.
    Article of note: "Stair Banks Miami, FL."
  - Tin House Magazine. Volume One: Number One. New York: McCormack Communications, Spring 1999. pp. 192. (Box 6, Folder 212)
    Edited by Win McCormack.
    Contributions by Ariel Dorfman, James Kelman, Rick Moody and Francine Prose.
    Article of note: "Rebecca West's Nuremberg Trial Coverage."
    Design by Jon Baird.
  - Trace: AIGA Journal of Design. Volume One: Number One. New York: AIGA, 2001. pp. 124. (Box 6, Folder 213)
    Edited by Andrea Codrington.
    Contributions by Steven Heller, Matt Soar, Scott Stowell and Tom Vanderbilt.
    Article of note: "Designed to Deceive."
    Design by 2x4.
  - Transactions of the American Crystallographic Association. Issue 1. New York: American Crystallographic Association, February, 1965. pp. 112. (Box 6, Folder 214)
    Edited by S.C. Abrahams.
    Contributions by B. W. Batterman, W. H. Zachariasen and R. A. Young.
    Article of note: "Extinction."
  - Trips. Number One. San Francisco: Banana Republic, Spring 1988. pp. 160. (Box 6, Folder 215)
    Edited by Mel Ziegler and Carolyn White.
    Contributions by Richard Ford, Charlie Haas and Mark Jacobson.
    Article of note: "Little Rock in the Fifties."
    Design by Roger Black.
  - A Typographic Quest. Number One. West Virginia: West Virginia Pulp and Paper, 1964. pp. 28. (Box 6, Folder 216)
    Edited by Carl Dair.
    Article of note: "Old Style Faces."
    Design by Carl Dair.
  - Typographica. New Series: Number One. London: Lund Humphries, June 1960. pp. 64. (Box 6, Folder 217)
    Edited by Herbert Spencer.
    Contributions by Alan Bartram, Henri Friedlaender and Penuel Peter Kahane.
    Article of note: "The History of Numerals."
    Cover design by Anne Hickmott.
  - Typographische Monatsblätter. Number One. Zurich: Union Comedia of Switzerland for the Advancement of Education, January 2000. pp. 48. (Box 6, Folder 218)
    Edited by Jean-Pierre Graber.
    Contributions by Christoph Bignens, Roger Chatelain and Helmut Schmid.
    Article of note: "Richard Paul Lohse as Graphic Designer."
    Special issue of Swiss Typographic Magazine inspired by Typographische Monatsblätter, Number One, 1943.
  - Unit: Design/Research. Number One. London: Unit Editions, 2010. pp. 64. (Box 6, Folder 219)
    Edited by Tony Brook and Adrian Shaughnessy.
    Design by David McFarline and Claudia Klat, Spin.
  - Uniqlo Paper. Issue 1. New York: Uniqlo, Fall/Winter 2006. pp. 98. (Box 7, Folder 266)
    Articles of note: "I Love New York" and "Ode to Tokyo."
  - University Business. Volume 1: Number 1. New York: University Business, March/April 1998. pp. 72. (Box 6, Folder 220)
    Edited by Jeffrey Kittay.
    Contributions by Kathryn Beaumont, Donald Kennedy and Robert Rosenzweig.
    Article of note: "The Packaging of George Mason University: Lessons from an unremarkable school in the fine art of getting noticed."
  - Vanitas. Number One. New York: Vanitas, June 2005. pp. 140. (Box 6, Folder 221)
    Edited by Vincent Katz.
    Contributions by Jordan Davis, Ann Lauterbach and Carter Ratcliff.
    Article of note: "Peeling Oranges on Top of the Skyscrapers."
    Cover by Jim Dine.
  - Varoom. Issue 01. London: Association of Illustrators, 2006. pp. 88. (Box 7, Folder 267)
    Edited by Adrian Shaughnessy.
    Contributions by Steven Heller, Alice Tremlow and John O'Reilly.
    Article of note: "Thinking Through Making: An Interview with Dan Fern."
    Design by Non-Format.
  - Venue: An International Literary Magazine. Number One. Amsterdam: Overseas Publishers Association, 1997. pp. 176. (Box 6, Folder 222)
    Edited by John Brenkman.
    Contributions by Jeffery Renard Allen, Wayne Koestenbaum and Orphan Pamuk.
    Article of note: "Trans-Chinese: Notes on Language and Sensibility."
    Design by Terry Berkowitz.
  - Verdant: Smarter Choices for Better Living. Premiere Issue. New York: Verdant Magazine. pp. 104., undated (Box 6, Folder 223)
    Edited by Sharon King Hoge.
    Contributions by Christopher Buckley, Rosemary Black and Maureen Gilmer.
    Article of note: "Green Investing: Coming of Age."
    Design by Ivy Tashlik.
  - Vintage Magazine. Premiere Issue. New York: Vintage Magazine, 2009. pp. 90. (Box 6, Folder 224)
    Edited by Ivy Baer Sherman.
    Contributions by Judith Oksner, Barbara Lippert and Jack Hassid.
    Article of note: "From Rags to Riches: The Dirty Story Behind Sugar Refining in 19th Century New York City."
  - W Magazine: A Quarterly Magazine from Waterstone's. Volume One. Brentford, England: Waterstone's, Spring 1995. pp. 86. (Box 6, Folder 225)
    Edited by Waterstone's.
    Contributions by Richard Avedon, Simon Callow and Gabriel Garcia Márquez.
    Article of note: "Gabriel Garcia Márquez."
    Cover photograph by Douglas Brothers.
  - Wholphin. Number 1. San Francisco: McSweeney's Publishing, 2005. (Box 6, Folder 226)
    Edited by Brett Hoff.
    Contributions by Spike Jonze, Brian Dewan and Jeroen Offerman.
    Film of note: "Al Gore Documentary."
  - Wigwag. Volume One: Number One. New York: Wigwag, October 1989. pp. 96. (Box 6, Folder 227)
    Edited by Alexander Kaplen.
    Contributions by Randy Cohen, Carmen Delzell and Witold Rybczynski.
    Article of note: "The Private Ministry of Colonel Thieme."
  - Wired. Premier Issue. San Francisco: Wired USA, 1993. pp. 112. (Box 6, Folder 228)
    Edited by Louis Rossetto.
    Contributions by Sewart Brand, John Browning and Fred Davis.
    Article of note: "If Your Toaster Had a Brain."
    Design by Plunkett + Kuhr.
  - Word & Image: A Journal of Verbal / Visual Enquiry. Volume One: Number One. Norwich, England: University of East Anglia, January–March 1985. pp. 134. (Box 6, Folder 229)
    Edited by John Dixon Hunt and Michael Leslie.
    Contributions by Robert Druce, Paul Holberton and Dean Tolle Mace.
    Article of note: "Ut pictura poesis, ut pictura hortus, and the picturesque."
  - World Affairs: A Journal of Ideas and Debate. Re-Design Launch Issue. [Volume 170: Number 3.] Washington, DC: Heldref, Winter 2008. pp. 108. (Box 6, Folder 230)
    Edited by Lawrence F. Kaplan.
    Contributions by Christopher Hitchens, Peter Collier and Richard H. Kohn.
    Article of note: "Dear Mr President..."
    Design by Robert F. Azarcon.
  - World Magazine. Volume One: Number One. New York: World, July 1972. pp. 132. (Box 6, Folder 231)
    Edited by Norman Cousins.
    Contributions by Santi Tara, U Thant and Roger M. Williams.
    Article of note: "What Happened to Graham Greene's Haiti?"
    Design by Marcia Gloster McElrath.
  - World Politics: A Quarterly Journal of International Relations. Volume One: Number One. New Haven: Yale Institute of International Studies, October 1948. pp. 152. (Box 6, Folder 232)
    Edited by William T. R. Fox.
    Contributions by Waldemar Gurian, Hans Morgenthau and Jacob Viner.
    Article of note: "Power Versus Plenty as Objectives of Foreign Policy in the Seventeenth and Eighteenth Centuries."
  - Worldbusiness: The Global Perspective. Volume One: Number One. New York: KPMG Peat Marwick, January 1995. pp. 48. (Box 6, Folder 233)
    Edited by John Van Doorn. Contributions by L. J. Davis, John Whalen and Bernard Simon.
    Article of note: "Rupert the First."
    Design by Frankfurt Balkind Partners.
  - XX!st Century. Number One. New York: Rizzoli, Winter 1991–1992. pp. 120. (Box 7, Folder 268)
    Contributions by Ian Buruma, Gregory Crewdson, Christopher Hitchens, David Rieff and Peter Sellers.
    Article of note: "Marshmallow Bombs + Cameras and Computers: The New Technology of Invisible Deception."
    Design by José Conde.
  - Zodiac: An International Review of Architecture. New Series: Number One. Milan: Zodiac Architecture, February 1989. pp. 198. (Box 6, Folder 234)
    Edited by Guido Canella.
    Contributions by Richard Meier, Aldo Rossi and Manfredo Tafuri.
    Article of note: "Urban Development Strategies in Renaissance, Italy."
  - Zoetrope: Short Stories. Volume One: Number One. New York: AZX Publications, Winter 1997. pp. 58. (Box 7, Folder 269)
    Edited by Francis Coppola, Adrienne Brodeur and Elizabeth Lea Carpenter.
    Contributions by Nicola Barker, Joseph Chaikin, Mary Orr and Sam Shepard.
    Article of note: "What Happens Next? Hollywood and the Short Story."
    Design by Slatoff + Cohen Partners.
- 2012 Addition, 1917-2011
  - 100% Sound. Issue 01. India: Hundred Percent Zine, 2011. pp. 22. (Box 8, Folder 272)
    Scope and Contents note
    Edited by Sameer Kulavoor and Lokesh Karekar.
    Contributions by Nitin Jadhav, Lokesh Karekar and Deshna Mehta.
    Artist of note: Sourabh Thakur.
    Design by Sameer Kulavoor and Lokesh Karekar.
  - Annals of Medical History. Volume One. New York: Paul B. Hoeber, 1917. pp. 442. (Box 8, Folder 273)
    Edited by Francis R. Packard, M.D.
    Contributions by Fielding H. Garrison, Enricus Cordus and Pearce Baily.
    Article of note: "Voltaire's Relation to Medicine."
  - Baseline: International Typographics Magazine. Issue One. London: TSI Typographic Systems International, 1979. pp. 16. (Box 8, Folder 274)
    Edited by Mike Daines.
    Contribution by Maxwell J. Baumwell.
    Article of note: "Frederic W. Goudy: Master Type Designer."
    Design by TSI Typographic Systems International Limited.
  - The Bold Italic. Vol. 1. San Francisco: The Bold Italic, 2011. pp. 44. (Box 7, Folder 271)
    Edited by Emily Hiligoss and Linda Moore.
    Contributions by Broke-Ass Stuart, Juan Leguizamon and Elia Varela Serra.
    Article of note: "Living in San Francisco Means…Having a Crush on the Girl at Tartine."
    Design by Elizabeth Brown and Indhira Rojas/Design Theorem.
  - Chicago Works 01. Number 1. Chicago: Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago, 2011. pp. 8. (Box 8, Folder 275)
    Edited by Kate Steinmann.
    Contributions by Scott Reeder and Julie Rodrigues Widholm.
    Artist of note: Scott Reeder.
    Design by James Goggin.
  - Connecticut Jewish History. Number 1. West Hartford, CT: Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford, 1990. pp. 88. (Box 8, Folder 276)
    Edited by Lothar Kahn.
    Contributions by David G. Dalin, Abraham A. Ribicoff and Jack Zaiman.
    Article of note: "Autobiographical Sketch: Abraham A. Ribicoff."
    Design by Jim Rigby.
  - The D-Crit Florilegium. Number 1. New York: School of Visual Arts, 2010. pp. 12. (Box 8, Folder 277)
    Contributions by Hala Abdulmalak, Amelia Black and John Cantwell.
    Article of note: "Bacteria Building for Sustainability: The Convergence of Design and Biology in the 21st Century."
  - Design Philosophy Papers. Collection One. Ravensbourne, Australia: Team D/E/S, 2004. pp. 88. (Box 8, Folder 278)
    Edited by Anne-Marie Willis.
    Contributions by Tony Fry, Ezio Manzini and Cameron Tonkenwise.
    Article of note: "Scenarios of Sustainable Wellbeing."
  - eQ. Issue 001. Beverly, MA: Sappi, 2009. pp. 8. (Box 8, Folder 279)
    Contribution by Laura Thompson.
    Article of note: "Hearst: A Sustainability Story That Has No Ending."
  - The Form and the Frame. Edition One. Eindhoven, Netherlands: Onomatopee, 2010. (Box 8, Folder 280)
    Edited by Freek Lomme.
    Contributions by Bart Groenedaal, Kim de Groot and Merijn Oudenampsen.
    Article of note: "Ideology and Media."
    Design by Marjolein Delhaas.
  - Fresh Dialogue One: New Voices in Graphic Design. One. New York: Princeton Architectural Press, 2000. pp. 132. (Box 8, Folder 281)
    Edited by Beth Harrison.
    Contributions by Paula Scher, Nicholas Blechman and Christoph Niemann.
    Article of note: "Fresh Dialogue One: Transcript, May 26, 1999."
    Design by Sara E. Stemen.
  - Kyoorius Design Magazine. Launch Issue. Mumbai: Transasia Fine Papers Pvt Ltd, 2006. pp. 96. (Box 8, Folder 282)
    Edited by Rajesh Kejriwal.
    Contributions by Design Temple, Grandmother India and Eureka Moment Design Company.
    Article of note "The future starts here but where are we heading?"
    Design by Aziza Iqbal.
  - If/Then: Design Implications of New Media. Amsterdam: Netherlands Design Institute, 1999. pp. 264 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    Edited by Janet Abrams.
    Contributions by Malcolm McCullough, Mathilda Blyth and Sharon Lockhart.
    Article of note: "Knowledge Maps."
    Design by Mevis & Van Deursen.
  - Iridescent: Icograda Journal of Design Research. Volume 1. Italy: Fabrica, 2011. pp. 216. (Box 8, Folder 284)
    Edited by Max Bruinsma.
    Contributions by Bernard J. Canniffe, Russell Kennedy and Elizabeth (Dori) Tunstall.
    Article of note: "Design for Enabling Sustainable Livelihoods in Communities."
    Design by Arianna Di Betta, Michela Povoleri and Omar Vulpinari.
  - Journal of the Kafka Society of America. Number 1 and 2. New York: Kafka Society of America, 2002. pp. 84. (Box 8, Folder 285)
    Edited by Maria Luise Caputo-Mayr.
    Contributions by Peter U. Beicken, Beth Hawkins and Anthony Johae.
    Article of Note: "Sisyphus was a Bachelor:" Sexual Dreams and Fiction in Kafka."
  - Magistra: A Journal of Women's Spirituality in History. No.1. Atlanta: 1995. pp. 190. (Box 8, Folder 286)
    Edited by Judith Sutera and Deborah Vess.
    Contributions by Roger Corless, Ellen Oak and Roger Schoenbechler.
    Article of note: "The Androgynous Mysticism of Julian of Norwich."
  - Makeshift: A Journal of Hidden Creativity. Issue 01. Analogue Digital, Fall 2011. pp. 56. (Box 8, Folder 287)
    Edited by Niti Bhan.
    Contributions by Lynnette Chan, Steve Daniels and Myles Estey.
    Article of note: "Science of Scarcity."
    Illustration by Dadu Shin.
  - The Mid-Century. Number 1. New York: The Mid-Century Book Society, Inc., 1959. pp. 30. (Box 8, Folder 288)
    Edited by W.H. Auden, Jacques Barzun and Lionel Trilling.
    Contributions by the same.
    Article of note: "Agee on the Movies."
    Design by John Morning.
  - multipliCITY: Newsletter of the Pratt Graduate Center for Planning and the Environment. Issue 1. Brooklyn: Pratt Institute, Summer 2009. pp. 12. (Box 8, Folder 289)
    Edited by Simon Kawitzky.
    Contributions by John Shapiro, Ronald Shiffman and Simon Kawitzky.
    Article of note: "Pratt Initiative for Arts, Community and Social Change Addresses Interdisciplinary Work, Food Justice and More."
    Design by Simon Kawitzky.
  - the noble savage. Volume One. New York: Meridian Books, 1960. pp. 256. (Box 8, Folder 290)
    Edited by Saul Bellow, Keith Botsford, Jack Ludwig.
    Contributions by John Berryman, Ralph Ellison and Arthur Miller.
    Article of note: "Please Don't Kill Anything."
    Design by Elaine Lustig.
  - Providence: Studies in Western Civilization. Number 1. Providence, RI: Providence College Press, 1992. pp. 120. (Box 8, Folder 291)
    Edited by Leonard P. Hindsley.
    Contributions by Christopher Lasch, Henrique Urbano and Luciano Pereña Vicente.
    Article of note: "Persons, Sex and Family."
    Design by Joseph Gilbert.
  - RADAR. Number One. León, Spain: Museo de Arte Contemporáneo de Castilla y León, 2010. pp. 104. (Box 8, Folder 292)
    Edited by Augustin Pérez Rubio.
    Contributions by Rosina Cazali, Nicolás Guanini and Andrea Giunta.
    Article of note: "Arte y Biopolítica."
    Design by ActarBirkhäuserPro.
  - Reason. Vol. 1. Minneapolis: AIGA Minnesota, 2002-2003. pp. 82. (Box 8, Folder 293)
    Edited by Heather West Public Relations.
    Contributions by Scott Geiger, Jennifer Kane and Heather West.
    Article of note: "The Bold New Face of the World Cup."
    Design by Reason Project Team and Amy Anderson.
  - Russell: The Journal of Bertrand Russell Archives. Number One. Ontario: McMaster University Library Press, Spring 1971. pp. 12. (Box 8, Folder 294)
    Edited by William Ready.
    Contributions by Kenneth Blackwell, John G. Slater and B. J. Lucas.
    Article of note: "Bertrand Russell and The Tribunal."
  - Spartan Holiday. No. 1. U.S.A.: Ulcer City, 2012. pp. 36. (Box 8, Folder 295)
    Contribution by D.B. Dowd.
    Article of note: "Shanghai Pictorial."
    Design by Scott Gericke and Dave Maupin.
  - Supersudaca Reports. #1. pp. 24., undated (Box 8, Folder 296)
    Edited by Juan Pablo Corvalan, Felix Madrazo and Manuel de Rivero.
    Contributions by Martin Delgado, Mario Marchant and Esteban Varela.
    Article of note: "Montevideo Cooperativo: Gustavo Gonzalez Interview."
    Design by Juan Pablo Corvalan, Natalia Gajardo and Ingrid Sepulveda/SuSuKa.
  - West 86th: A Journal of Decorative Arts, Design, History, and Material Culture. Volume 18. Number 1. Chicago: University of Chicago Press, 2011. pp. 136. (Box 8, Folder 297)
    Edited by Paul Stirton
    Contributions by Marta Filipova, Alexander Watt and Nick Pearce.
    Article of note: "Shanghai 1908: A. W. Bahr and China's First Art Exhibition."
    Design by Laura Grey.
    [First issue to replace Studies in the Decorative Arts.]
- 2013 Addition, 1991-2004
  - ACME Novelty Library ("Jimmy Corrigan: The Smartest Kid on Earth"). Issue Number One. Seattle, WA: Fantagraphics Books, Winter 1993-94, Second Big Printing, December 1995. unpaged. (Box 8, Folder 298)